outerinner.com 2016-10-08

# Privacy Policy

###### Happy St.Patrick's Day

17% off on every order with code 'lucky17'

In order to offer you pleasant shopping experiences, OuterInner does collect personally identifiable information as well as log aggregate shopping information. We recognize we must maintain and use customer information responsibly. We respect your privacy and will never sell your information to any third party.

 **1\. What personal information is collected and how is it used?**  
After registering in OuterInner, we will know your email address. This email is only used to log in your account and inform you of your order status and OuterInner newsletters. If you place an order, we will get your order information and postal address, which are only available for this deal. We respect your privacy and will never sell your information to any third party. If you want to know more information about it, please check third party as below.

 **2\. Security**  
OuterInner.com is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site, when we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial or health information, we redirect visitors to a secure server. It is encrypted through industry-standard encryption technology known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL). Depending on your browser, this SSL will have encryption keys of up to 128 bits. Only parties responsible for processing your order have access to your credit card and bank information.  
Some firewalls do not permit communication through secure servers. In this case, you will not be able to connect to the secure server and must disable your firewall or choose a different method to order.

 **3\. Communication & Marketing (Opt in or out)**  
If you are one of our members, we will occasionally update you on our latest products, promotion news and special offers via emails, posts. However if you do not like being informed, please send message to [help@outerinner.com](mailto:help@outerinner.com). You can also access 'Your Account' to amend [Communication Preference](http://new.outerinner.com/account/register "OuterInner Login Communication Preference") once you [register ](http://new.outerinner.com/account/register "Register to OuterInner")and [login](http://new.outerinner.com/account/register "Login to OuterInner"). Or click on the "[unsubscribe](http://outerinner.dmdelivery.cn/x/c/?BcHdCoIwGADQV_nKu9xP5jT4iGBdGFhkUNRN_DNyNteazurp1zk1UN8Dib0FgiMceQWU_BbacTQrhF5uFFZqLWzY9I1QchL2F9YafZFR7iE1Wpt92QtwenDVUFtZiSDPeJFxOLEruZvUlrSjU9JdcM63n0MRdm9aZMfNDsfBDeYkwQvGWEoT3wDPuZL6OSNLP5zhDwu97)" link in any email communications which might we send to you.

 **4\. Cookies**  
A web tracking cookie is a bit of electronic information that a website or web browser can place on your computer's hard drive in order to do specific jobs like remembering your preferences or shopping cart contents.  
With cookies, OuterInner will be able to deliver a more customized and complete shopping experience to track visits from our partners and to enable the use of our shopping bag. For instance, we use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time when you visit our site. Please be assured that we will never use cookies to track any information about other sites you may visit or to collect any additional personal information.  
Although most browsers automatically accept cookies, you can usually change your web browser's preferences to block cookies or notify whenever you are sent a cookie.

 **5\. Links to other sites (third party)**  
With respect to Ad Servers: OuterInner do not join hands with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. We will not pass on any of your personal information to any third party.  
OuterInner may contain links to our partner networks, advertisers and other third parties. Please be aware that our site is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware while following a link to any of these websites, please note that they have their own privacy policies, which we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before submitting any personal data to these websites. This privacy statement only applies to OuterInner.com.

 **6\. Accessing and updating personal information**  
After created OuterInner account, you have the absolute right to access your personal information which been collected by register and either to modify this information if it is inaccurate or to delete all your account date at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. For account cancelling issue, please [contact us](http://new.outerinner.com/pages/customer-service "Contact OuterInner"). You can either call 1(813) 358 3228 or write to Leading Marketing Holding Ltd., 15/F., Highgrade Building, 117 Chatham Road, Tsimshatsui, Kowloon, Hongkong.
